stik.com 2018-03-04

# Stik.com

This Privacy Policy describes Stik's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information when you use the Stik Service. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Use.

* ## Information Collection and Use

Stik uses information we collect to connect users with others in their networks, communicate with users, analyze how the Service is used, diagnose service or technical problems, maintain security, personalize content, remember information to help you efficiently access your account, monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns, and track User Content and users as necessary to comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act and other applicable laws.

* ## User-Provided Information

You provide us information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address, and names of individuals in your online networks, if you sign up for an account with the Service (including by adding a Stik application on or connecting to the Service through a third-party service). When you connect your social media account to your Service profile, we collect information about you from that social media website. For example, when you connect your Facebook account, we may collect the information you have made publicly available in Facebook, such as your name, profile picture, cover photo, username, gender, friend networks, age range, locale, friend list, and any other information you have made public. We may also ask your permission to collect other information, such as your email address. When you make payments through the Service, you may need to provide financial account information, such as your credit card number, to our third-party service providers.

Your name and other information you choose to add to your profile will be available for public viewing on the Service. We may use your email address to send you Service-related notices (including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail). You can control receipt of certain Service-related messages on your Settings page. We may also use your contact information to send you marketing messages. If you do not want to receive such messages, you may opt out by following the instructions in the message. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses. We use information about your online networks and activities to connect you to others in your networks who we think may be of interest to you in connection with your use of the Service.

You also provide us information in User Content you post to the Service and features you use on the Service, such as endorsements. User Content you post to public areas of the Service and public actions you take on the Service may be publicly viewed on the Service and on the worldwide web.

The Service may permit you to invite friends to join the Service. If you choose to do so, we will use the email addresses and names you provide to send such invitations, and store this information to register your friends if your invitation is accepted and to track the success of our invitation service.

We may collect any information you provide through your communications with our customer-support team.

You consent to have your information shared with service providers and to be contacted by them by telephone or email, even if you have previously listed yourself on any corporate, state, or federal "do not call" list.

* ## Cookies

When you visit the Service, we may send one or more "cookies" - a small data file - to your computer to uniquely identify your browser and let Stik help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may convey anonymous information about how you browse the Service to us, but does not collect personal information about you. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser so that it can be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

* ## Log Files

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use the Service, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

* ## Clear Gifs Information

When you use the Service, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your Stik account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting and make Stik better for our users.

* ## Third Party Services

Stik uses third party analytics services to help understand use of the Service. These services collect the information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, including cookies and your IP address. Use of this information by each respective third party analytics service is governed by its privacy policy, and they may track your usage of other websites over time.

  1. ### Anonymous and Aggregate Data

We may anonymize and aggregate data collected through the Service and use it for any purpose.

* ## How We Share Your Information

  1. ### Personally Identifiable Information

Stik may share your personally identifiable and other information in connection with Stik's business, subject to any restrictions on disclosure imposed by the source from which you permitted Stik to collect the data (for instance, a social networking service). Examples of ways we might share your information include to connect you with opportunities we think may be of interest to you, or to share information about your activities on Stik back to your networks. For example, we may share your comments or endorsements with members of social networks. The Service may provide user settings that apply to certain types of information sharing. We may change the features and functionality of such settings from time to time. We cannot control third parties' use of your information.

In addition, Stik may share your personally identifiable information with our third party business partners for the purpose of providing the Service to you. If we do this, such third parties' use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Stik (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).

As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer or assign such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.

Stik may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Stik's rights or property.

We may disclose your personally identifiable and other information with your permission.

We do not rent, sell, or share personally identifiable information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, unless we have their permission.

  2. ### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Stik services.

Stik may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on Stik. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. Stik does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Stik to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. In addition, third-party advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites over time in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). The Stik Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers for more information. 

* ## How We Protect Your Information

Stik uses physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information and implement any privacy settings on the Service. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Stik or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Stik will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

* ## Your Choices About Your Information

You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Service, in which case Stik may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information and email preferences at any time by logging in to your account.

* ## Children's Privacy

Stik does not knowingly collect, maintain, use or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register with the Service. No part of the Service is directed to children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information.

* ## International Users

If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use, please note that you are agreeing to the transfer of your information to the United States and processing globally. By providing your information you consent to any transfer and processing in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

* ## Links to Other Websites

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from the Service, nor the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including those that have a link on our website, is subject to that website's own rules and policies.

* ## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on this page to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@stik.com](mailto:privacy@stik.com) or send mail to: Stik, Attention: Privacy, 1528 Woodward Ave, Detroit, MI 48226.
